askdanandjennifer.com 2007-12-11

# Privacy Policy

You are here >

[Home](http://www.askdanandjennifer.com/ "Browse to: Home") / Privacy Policy 

We at AskDanAndJennifer.com ("we" or "AskDanAndJennifer.com") havecreated this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment toprotecting your personal information and informing you about how wehandle it. This privacy policy only applies to transactions andactivities in which you engage and data gathered on theAskDanAndJennifer.com Website, but does not apply to any other Websiteor offline point of contact between AskDanAndJennifer.com, or any othercompany, and consumers. Please review this privacy policy periodicallyas we may modify it from time to time. This privacy policy was lastrevised on September 8, 2006. Each time you visit the Site or provideus with information, by doing so you are accepting the practicesdescribed in this privacy policy at that time. 

### Use of Information Obtained by AskDanAndJennifer.com  

### Private Information

We use email addresses submitted by customers only in privatecorrespondence with our customers. We will never sell or give away youremail address. Financial information that is collected is used to billthe customer for purchases. All other private information submitted bythe customer is confidential and will not be disclosed except asrequired by law or to protect customers of AskDanAndJennifer.com. 

### Public Information

Your IP Address Like most e-commerce Websites, each time you visitthe Site, we automatically collect your IP address and the web pagefrom which you came. In order to administer and optimize the Site foryou and to diagnose problems with our Site, we use your IP address tohelp identify you and to gather broad demographic information aboutyou. 

### Cookies

Like most Websites, the Site uses cookies to keep track of yourpurchases and other activity on the Site and enhance your experience onthe Site. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to yourinterests, to save your password, and if you choose, to save otherpersonal and financial information so you do not have to reenter iteach time you visit the Site. Third party advertisers on the Site mayalso place or read cookies on your browser. If you wish to disablethese cookies, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers willtell you how. However, if you set your browser to disable cookies, youmay not be able to access certain areas on the Site. Our SecurityPrecautions The Site has security measures in place to protect againstthe loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.Our secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard and among thebest software available today for secure commerce transactions. Weencrypt all of your personal and financial information as it travelsover the Internet and we store your financial information on ourservers in encrypted form. Your information may be transferred to andmaintained on computer networks which may be located outside of thestate, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction in whichyou reside, and the country or jurisdiction in which these computernetworks are located may not have privacy laws as protective as thelaws in your country or jurisdiction. 

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy,the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Site, you cancontact us at [support@Dan-and-Jennifer.com](mailto:support@Dan-and-Jennifer.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).
